One of my favorite jazz songs of all time.
You do whatever's necessary.
Sang by Abbey Lincoln.
It's Brother Can You Spare a Dime.
Once I built a railroad.
Made it run.
Made it race against time.
Once I built a railroad.
Now it's done.
Brother Can You Spare a Dime.
Once I built a tower.
To the sun.
Brick and rivet and line.
Once I built a tower.
Now it's done.
Brother Can You Spare a Dime.
Once in khaki suits.
Gee, we looked swell.
Full of that Yankee doodle dee dum.
Half a million boots went slogging through hell.
I was the kid with the drum.
Say, don't you remember?
They called me out.
It was out all the time.
Say, don't you remember?
I'm your path.
Can you spare?
A Dime.
Buddy, can you spare?